So let's have a look at the integration between Bedrock and CloudWatch logs.
So we're going to go under Settings on the bottom left,
and you have Model Invocation Logging.
So here we can definitely enable it,
and then this is going to collect all metadata requests and responses
for all model invocations in your accounts.
So you can select the type of data you want to include with logs,
so it could be text, images, and embeddings.
And then the destination could be Amazon as free buckets,
or it could be CloudWatch only, or it could be both.
So I'm just going to use CloudWatch only,
and then you need to specify a log group name.
So I call this one Bedrock Invocation Logging.
And then I will create a user in your role.
So this is the role that Amazon Bedrock will need to send data to CloudWatch logs.
So I call this one Bedrock Invocation Logging Role.
OK.
And next, we have, as relocation for larger deliveries.
So in case it's over 100 kilobytes, then it can be published to Amazon as free.
But we don't need this right now, so we're going to just save these settings.
So we get an error saying the specified log group doesn't exist.
So we have to create it manually in CloudWatch in this instance.
Maybe this will be fixed by the time you use this.
But let's go into CloudWatch logs, log groups.
And then you're going to create a new log group.
And the name is going to be this one that I'm going to copy and paste.
So we can set up some settings.
Do you want the log to expire or not?
But we're just going to click on Create and get going.
OK, so now my log group is created.
It is here.
And let's go ahead in Amazon Bedrock.
And we're going to save these settings one more time.
And we now need to say that we won't use an existing service role.
That is right here.
So let me refer to this.
This is sometimes a bit annoying when you have issues on the console.
But it was may fix this at some point.
So here we go.
Now we have select the existing role that has been created and save the settings.
And we should be good to go.
OK, so the settings have been saved successfully.
And what I can do now, as I can go in chat, I will select a model.
And I will just click on Run.
And then we're going to get-- so we send an input.
And then we get an output.
And we're good to go.
Now let's wait a little bit.
And then go into CloudWatch logs to see if it appears.
So I'm going into CloudWatch logs.
And we refresh this page.
And we have one log stream here.
Give us bedrock model invocations.
And here we have the information that the permissions have set correctly for Amazon bedrock logs.
And then we get some information about a model invocation.
So we get a lot of information around it.
But we know that, for example, the model ID is Amazon Titan Text Express V1.
This is a way for us to identify the models that we're using.
We get information about the region.
And then we get the messages.
So we have a user that's us.
And we sent this input.
And then we have some information around the configuration for this invocation.
And how many tokens was it, 271?
And the output is this message.
So the assistant role means that it's the model itself and the content is this.
And so again, we get the information that the latency was 4,38 millisecond.
We get information around the output token.
The total token and so on.
So this is very helpful because, as you can see, a lot of information is included here.
And we can use this information later on to debug everything.
For example, we could, for example, run an alarm.
And to look at if the latency is always beneath a specific number.
And if one day the latency reaches a high number, then we may want to send an alert saying,
hey, your latency requirements are a little too high now.
And the user experience may be degraded.
So that's the way of doing it.
But hopefully you get the idea of integrating Amazon bedrock with CloudWatch logs.
So the other thing we can do is go into CloudWatch and go into all metrics and
then click on bedrock.
And you may have more metrics than me, but we have here metrics by model ID.
You can look at it or across all model ID.
And for example, we can have a look at the number of invocations or for
example, the invocation latency. And we can see here that the latency is being plotted on
this graph. So now, of course, if you have a sustained usage of Amazon bedrock,
then you will see a curve here with multiple data points.
But a lot of metrics are being sent by bedrock into CloudWatch metrics.
And you can then build metrics, graphs, dashboards and alarms on top of it as well.
In case, for example, the invocation latency gets too high.
So let's say for this lecture, I hope you liked it.
and I will see you in the next lecture.